skydaz.com 2017-12-23

# Skydaz – Privacy Policy

* * *

We here at Skydaz greatly respect your privacy and we hope that our users feel that the information they share with us is 100% secure and private. Here are the guidelines we follow at Skydaz to ensure your privacy and our integrity:

## Email

We will never share your email with third parties. It will only be used for replying to your comments and or suggestions and sometime important news & announcements which you can opt out of.

## Passwords

Skydaz staff will NEVER ask for your password. If someone does ask for your password or other info, please immediately notify us.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Skydaz is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

## Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/ "Network Advertising"). You can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the news so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

## Final Notes

Skydaz.com will never, under any circumstances give away or display your IP address to third parties. Additionally, Skydaz will never sell or transmit e-mail addresses or any other personal identifiers to 3rd parties.  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to [Contact Us](http://www.skydaz.com/contact-skydaz/)! Thank you for your cooperation.
